crystalheels.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy | CrystalHeels.com

This privacy policy sets out how Crystal Heels LLC uses and protects any information that you give Crystal Heels LLC when you use this website.

Crystal Heels LLC is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Crystal Heels LLC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01/31/2011.

**The information we collect**

Generally, you may browse the Web Site without providing any personally identifiable information. However, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information at various times and places on this Web Site. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you may not be able to access all of this Web Site or participate in all of its features.

We receive and store any personally identifiable information you enter on the Web Site, whenever you shop with Crystal Heels - online, through our catalogs, or in our stores, or information you give us in any other way, such as by subscribing to our catalogs or emails. For example, we may collect the following personally identifiable information: your name, address, telephone number, mobile telephone number, driver's license number, birth date, and e-mail address. If you use a credit or debit card or pay by check, we will also include your account number.

When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information, such as your favorite designers.

If you use one of our services, or participate in one of our surveys, promotions, or sweepstakes, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, interests or product preferences.

From your purchases and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.

When you visit this Web Site, our web server automatically collects anonymous information such as log data and IP addresses. We may use the automatically collected information for a number of purposes, such as improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions.

**How we use the information we collect**

We use the information we collect for various purposes, including:

  * to complete your purchase transactions
  * to provide the services you request
  * to send you our catalogs and other offerings by mail or email
  * to keep you informed about the status of your orders
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you
  * to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased
  * to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall shopping experience

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

·  whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

·  if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [[email protected]](http://crystalheels.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2a43444c456a495853595e4b46424f4f465904494547)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [[email protected]](http://crystalheels.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#234a4d454c6340515a5057424f4b46464f500d404c4e0d)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
